<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>1trickPwnyta's Defaults</name>
	<author>1trickPwnyta</author>
	<packageId>defaults.1trickPwnyta</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
Tired of having to go through the same ritual every time you start a new colony of configuring your colonists' schedules, setting your quest reward preferences, turning down the medicine setting so you don't waste your good medicine on bruises, and more? This mod allows you to customize various default settings to use during gameplay, such as the default schedules your colonists will assume. See below for a full list of settings.

Supports all DLC and can be safely added mid-playthrough, however many settings will only apply to new colonies.

Full list of settings:
  - Storyteller settings: Allows you to set the default storyteller/difficulty settings to use for a new colony, including custom difficulty settings.
  - World settings: Allows you to set the default world settings to use for a new colony.
  - Colonist schedules: Allows you to set custom default schedules for colonists. You can create alternating schedules and the mod will cycle between them when assigning them to new colonists.
  - Medicine settings: Allows you to set the default medicine settings to use for a new colony.
  - Reward preferences: Allows you to set the default reward preferences to use for a new colony.
  - Expanded resource categories: Allows you to set which resource tree categories are expanded by default in categorized mode.
  - Stockpile zone types: Allows you to configure the default settings for stockpile zones and dumping stockpile zones. You can also create your own custom stockpile zone types with their own settings.
  - Default hostility response: Allows you to set the default hostility response to use for new colonists.
  - Default medicine to carry: Allows you to set the default medicine type that new colonists will carry (if you assign them to carry any).
  - Default auto rebuild setting: Allows you to set the default auto-rebuild setting to use for a new colony.
  - Default auto home area setting: Allows you to set the default auto-home area setting to use for a new colony.
  - Use manual work priorities by default: You can do this.
  - Default plant type: Allows you to set the default plant type for new growing zones.

=== Updates ===
07/23/2024: Fixed bug that caused incompatibility with the Blueprints mod, added error handling for situations where previously installed mods or DLCs are removed.
	</description>
	<url>https://github.com/1trickPwnyta/DefaultsMod</url>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
